Guide to the Felipe Ehrenberg Papers, ca. 1964-2000
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondencia
  - Subseries 1A. Professional and Personal
    - Macotela, Gabriel (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Macotela, (Babel) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Manrique, Daniel ( Tepito Arte Aca) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Maravalhas, Nelson Junior (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Marcos (Grupo de Arte) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Marcos, Jesus (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Marichal, Julia (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Marin, Manuel (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mariscal, Carmen (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Marmata, Francisco (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Marquez, Rosa Luisa (Puerto Rico) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Martinez, Raul (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Martinez Castro, Agustin (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Martinez Diez, Luis Angel (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Martinez Duarte, Monica (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Martorell, Antonio (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Mayer, Monica (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Mayito (Mario Garcia Joya) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Medina, Zenobia (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Mendez Calvillo, Franco (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mendez, Caratini (pre-Mex.) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Menendez Navarette, Jose Rafael (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Meredith, Virginia R. (Alumna Chicago) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Mesa Baynes, Amalia (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mexic - Arte (Austin) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Meyers, Ralph [1] (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Meyers, Ralph [2] (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Minor, Flor (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Molina, Ernesto (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Mondragon, Sergio (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Morisset, Denys (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Munoz, Victor (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Navarro, Rafael (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - No-Grupo A (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - No-Grupo B (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Noe, Luis Felipe (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Norman, Carol (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Nunez, Victor Hugo (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Nyman, Michael (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - O'Gorman, Juan (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Orozco, Gabriel (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Orozco Ochoa, Victor (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Ortiz, Ruben (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ott, Werner (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Padin, Clemente (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Padin, Clemente: Textos Teoricos (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Padin / Caravallo (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Palau, Martha (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Palmer, Kathleen (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Parada, Esther (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Parra, Tomas (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Pascoe, Juan / Taller Martin Pescador (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Patino, Martha Elvira (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Patrix, Blaise (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Pecaninis, Yani (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Peredo, Melchor (Muralista Xalapeno) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Pitol, Sergio (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh State University (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Plant, John (Councillor) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Plazas Saboya, Hugo (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Polkinghorn, Harry (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Pomeroy, Jim (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Portillos, Alfredo (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Preux, Pedro (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Prieto, Antonio (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Prigoff, James, B. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Pyramid Atlantic (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Quintero Rivera, Angel ""Chuy"" (Puerto Rico) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Rahon, Alice (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Ramos Caro, Jorge Luis (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Randall, Margaret (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Raya, Marcos (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Reyes, Cordero (Chucho) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Reinhard, Rick and Judy (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Rodriguez-Del Paso, Joaquin (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Rolfe, Raul (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Romero, Alejandro (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Romero, Elizabeth (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ross, Elizabeth (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Roter, Janice (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Rotondo, Maribel (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Rovira, Xavier (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Ruiz-Rich, Cecelia (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Russell, Don (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Saiga, Kasumi (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Sampiero, Guillermo (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Santamaria, Elvira (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Sasidharan, M. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Sanchez, Jose (Chicano) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Sanchez Lopez, Elisa (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Sandoval, Mauricio (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Schimizu, Kumiko (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Sebastian Barbera, Juan (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Siegal, Larry (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Siegal, Laurence (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Sitting Dog [1] (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Sitting Dog [2] (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Skuta (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Melanie (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Pauline (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Soler, Jose (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Soruco, Raul (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Soto Millan, Eduardo (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Sperakis, Nicholas (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Springer, Jose Manuel (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Stampfl, Barry (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Stewart, Graham (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Stromberg, Gobi (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Suckaer, Ingrid (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Tarcisio, Eloy; Teruel, Encarnacion (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Tetenbaum, Barbara (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Third Text - Jean Fisher (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Sandra (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Tisa, Benedict (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Toledo, Francisco (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Trachtenberg, Alan [1] (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Trachtenberg, Alan [2] (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Trevi, Gloria (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Trevino, Milburgo (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Turok, Martha (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Valdez Diaz Velez, Jorge (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Valdez Perezgasca, Jose (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Van der Schelling, Bart (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Vargas, Eugenia (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Vater, Regina (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Vazquez, Carmen (Puerto Rico) (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Velasco, Alejandro (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Velasquez, Hugo (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Villareal, David; ""Ley Rock"" (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Villareal, Roman (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Villareal, Rogelio (posmoderna) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Vinicio, Marco (NY) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Viskin, Boris (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Weber, John Pitman (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Webster, Sande (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Wheeler, Susan (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Weiss, Rachel (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Winchester, Deal (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Xavier, Hector (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ybarra-Frausto, Tomas (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Zabala, Horacio (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Zannini, Walter (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Zavala, Manuel (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Zener, Carlos (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Zepeda, Antonio (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Zepeda, Eraclio (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Ziff, Trisa (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Sanchez-Aldana, Eugenio (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Schneemann, Carolee (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Weber, Marshall (Arists' Television Access, San Francisco) (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Zerpa, Carlos (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1B: International Organizations and Publications
    - The Americas Foundation (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - AVAC - Asociation Uruguaya de Artistas Correo (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Artmetropole (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Arts International (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Banff - Canada (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - C.A.Y.C. [Centro de Arte y Comunicacion] [1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - C.A.Y.C. [Centro de Arte y Comunicacion] [2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - C.A.Y.C. [Centro de Arte y Comunicacion] (Jorge Glusberg) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - C.A.Y.C. [Centro de Arte y Comunicacion] Video, etc. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Center of Photography at Woodstock, N.Y. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - DIA Art - Foundation (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - El Zocale (Ex-Mira) Gonzalez, Jose (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - ETA [Creative Arts Foundation] (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Exit Art - N.Y. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Fideicomiso Para LA Cultura Mex-USA (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - (Forum) Stadtpark [1 0f 2] (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - (Forum) Stadtpark [2 0f 2] (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Fullbright (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Galeria Inti (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Galeria La Raza (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Galpon (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Guggenheim [1 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Guggenheim [2 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Guggenheim [3 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - High Performance (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Kalejdoskkop - Sune Nordgren / Suecia (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Le Lieu (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - NAAO '85 [National Association of Artists' Organizations] (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - V Conference NAOO - LACE, 1988 [National Association of Artists Organizations, at Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions] (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - New Art Examiner (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - New Art Examiner, Phildelphia, May '85 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Nexus Contemporary Art Center (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - PCCLAS (XXXIV Reunion) [Pacific Coast Council on Latin American Studies] (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Peace Museum (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Puerto Rico - CEREP [Centro de Estudios de la Realidad Puertoriquena] (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Rutgers (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Art Institute (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Self Help Graphics (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Society for Photographic Education - Philadelphia (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Visual Studies Workshop (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - WPA - Viaje Washington 1985 [Washington Project for the Arts] (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Yellow Springs Institute (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Yellow Springs Pa, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - CIMCA [Centro de Integracion de Medios de Comunicacion Alternativa] - Gumico Dagron, Alfonso (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1C: National Organizations and Publications
    - Curare (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Alianza Civica (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Americop / Disenos (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Asociacion de Escritores de Mexico, A. C (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Asociacion Mexicana para la Rehabilitacion y Conservacion de Pistacidos (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Causa Ciudadana (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - CNC - Tribunas, etc. [National Peasant Confederation ] (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - COMEX - AMPA [Comercial Mexicana de Pinturas; Asociacion Mexicana de Pintores de Aerosografia] (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Conaculta / SNCA [Sistema Nacional de Creadores de Arte] (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Conaculta (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Conaculta / Racortes Relativos al CNCA / Otros (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Conaculta Reporte (1989) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Consejo Mexicano de Fotgrafia (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - El Archivero (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - El Zopilate, Grupo de Teatro (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Elefantes Iluminados (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Expo Arte Guadalajara (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Fraternidad de Reporteros de Mexico (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Frente Mexicano de Grupos de Trabajadores de la Cultura (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - I Foro Mex - EUA/Cronicas Fotograficas (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Grupo Proceso Pentagano (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Instituto de la Cultura de B.C. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - La Pus - Moderna, La Regla Rota (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Los Otros Editores (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Michoacan, Plasticos de (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Pascual - Coop / Fund Arte (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Poemex 2, Segunda Muestra de Poesia Visual en Mexico (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Poemex III, Bienal de Poesia Visual Experimental y Alternativa, 1990 (Espinosa, Cesar) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Poemex III, Bienal de Poesia Visual #2 - 1992, Rota la Logica (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Poemex III, Bienal de Poesia Visual #3, Material Diverso, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - IV Bienal de Poesia Visual/Experimental - 94 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Poesia Visual V Bienal, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Poemex, V Bienal de Poesia Visual/Experimental - 96 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Piecoa, S.A. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Pinto Mi Raya (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Promotora va por Cuba (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Ramirez, Fernando (Tepito desde El Zaguen) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - SOMAAP '97 - Estatutos [Sociedad Mexicana de Autores de las Artes Plasticas] (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - SOMAAP [Sociedad Mexicana de Autores de las Artes Plasticas] [1 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - SOMAAP [Sociedad Mexicana de Autores de las Artes Plasticas] [2 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - SOMART [Sociedad Mexicana de Artes] (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Temistocles 44 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1D: Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Ali, Fatima (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Anteo, Victor (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Antz, Michael (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Aragones, Sergio y Lilio (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Arau, Alfonso (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Barranco, Luis (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Baxter, Violet (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Bennett, Curtis (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Beswick, Collin (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Blake, Peter y Rosy (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - BOAC Cargo (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Boss, Roberto (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Brossard, Chandler (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Cartas Sueltas [miscellaneous correspondence 1960s - 1970s] (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Carr-Jones, Michael (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Carral, Jose (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Cevet, David (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cecena, Natacha (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Chile (Varios) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Costa Rica: Varios [Joaquin, Irene y Jose] (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Czeslaw, Irene (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - De Angeli, Jorge (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - De Avila, Rafael (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - De Landa, Carlos (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - De Swaan, Salomon (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Diaz Lastra, Alberto (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Dowdall, Vick (BBC TV) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Fahlender, Inger (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Farmer, Marjorie and Bill (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fibich, Felix and Judith (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Felshin, Anne (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Filcer, Luis (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Franceschini, Elizabeth (Tiffani) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Franco, Jean Ceres (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Freed, Frank and Eleanor (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Fuller, Stephen Kerr (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Genoves, Santiago (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Gerassi, John (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Godoy, Virginia (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Gomez Tagle, Silvia (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Graef, Roger (Allan King Associates) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Greenberg, Alvin (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Gutierrez, Heras Joaquin (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Heaman, Sam (Ridley) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Heidi (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Hollingshead, Michael (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Home Office (U.K.) (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Honigman, Richard (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - House, Linn (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Hughes, David, and Zetterling, Mai (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Jenkins, Ian (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Jones, Humphrey and Jenny (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - ""Jordaens"": Viaje (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Jorge Hiran [Torres Diaz, Jorge Hiran (?)] (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Kamerlink, Joyce (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Kaplow, Maurice (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Katziva, David (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Kaufman, Ed and Ellen (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Kessler, Arnold (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Kosloff (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Ladron de Guevera, Moises (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Landesman, Jay (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Landau, Dominique (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Larrauri, Alfredo S. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Leiterman, Richard (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Jeannie Scott (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Lillien, Otto and Lore (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Lopez Acosta, Rafael y Pillo (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Luciernaga, Gloria (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Magister Lupus, Tony (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Manfred, Ernest (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Mendelssohn, Lilian (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - [Unidentified sketches, maps, etc. found with Lilian Mendelssohn material; schoolwork from 1975?] (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Melo, Yolanda (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Nehemia, Reb (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Newman, Paul S. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Pietkiewicz, Hala (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Platzner, Heinz and Steffi (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Ridley College (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Rocha, Manuel (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Rueda, Victor (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Shaio, Patricia (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Siracusa, Rene (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Valjalo (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Van der Saar, Eric (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Vaque, don Ramon (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Velez, Richard (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Vicens, Luis (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Weinstein, David J. (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Wilkinson, John and Audrey (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Whitehead, Paul (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Wright, Terry (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Wybo, Luis (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 1E: Printouts of Email, Documents, and Other Miscellaneous Material Contained on Zip Disk
    - Asesorias - Jurados / 4°Piso Editores (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Araniva (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Calderon (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Defa Cultura (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Domecq (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Jurados (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / SOMAAP / Haciendas (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / SOMAAP / Reestruct (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / SOMAAP / Reportes (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / SOMAAP: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / TeVe (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Tlaxcala00 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Velez-JF (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / X-Teresa (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Asesorias - Jurados / Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - BGP [Beau Geste Press] (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Biografias / Acerca de FE (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Biografias / Entrevistas (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Biografias / Tesis (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Biografias / Tesis (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Biografias / Miscellanoeus Curriculum Vitae (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Biografias / Miscellanoeus biographical material (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Carmen / X-carmen.doc (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Clases / AVA / NuevoLeon / NLBola8 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Clases / AVA / NuevoLeon / NLRuc@s (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Clases / AVA / NuevoLeon / Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Clases / AVA / SLP (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Clases / AVA / Sonora (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Clases / AVA / Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Clases / Causas y Efectos (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Clases / CNCA etc. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Clases / Instalacion (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Clases / Labor Edit (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Clases / Performa (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Clases / Taller Tropicos (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Clases: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Coches (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Digital images of car ""art""
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Angloamerica / Canada (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Angloamerica / E.U.A. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Angloamerica: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Europa (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica / Argentina (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica / Brasil (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica / Brasil (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica / Uruguay (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica: Program de Cambio..MSG [1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 14)
      When opened, this file changes name to Uruguay-Arztegui.MSG
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Latinoamerica: Program de Cambio..MSG [2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Mexico [1 of 3] (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Mexico [2 of 3] (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondencia / Artistas / Mexico [3 of 3] (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Correspondencia / Bebis (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Correspondencia / Conn y familia (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Correspondencia / Critic-Histor (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Correspondencia: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondencia: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [2 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Dibujos / Calacas 00 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Dibujos: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Estampas (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Argentina (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Australia (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Brasil (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Canada (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Chicago (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Colombia / ColArena (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Colombia: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Costa Rica (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Cuba (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Dinamarca (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / Austin (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / California (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / Chicago (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / InSite (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / NewMexico (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / San Diego (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / Texas (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / Vermont (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-E.U.A. / Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Espana (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Inglaterra (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-RepDominicana (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Tijuana (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Uruguay (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Borges (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Embajada / Mus-A-Otero (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Embajada / MuseoCruzDiez (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Embajada / Valencia00 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Embajada: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / EPS Diversa00 / Puentes (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / EPS Diversa00: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Latincollector (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Museo Sefardi (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Subasta00 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Viaje-Nov-00 / Mus-A-Otero (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Viaje-Nov-00 / MuseoCruzDiez (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Viaje-Nov-00 / Valencia00 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Viaje-Nov-00: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Viart 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Felipe / A-Administracion / P-Venezuela / Miscellaneous mail, documents, etc. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Ficcion [1 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Ficcion [2 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - MexicoEterno00 (Box 33, Folder 4)